publicholidays.co.uk 2019-10-29

# Privacy Policy - PublicHolidays.co.uk

Start Planning

United Kingdom   

Your privacy is important to Public Holidays Global Pty Ltd (“Public Holidays Global”). This Privacy Policy covers what we collect and how we use, disclose, transfer and store your information.

**1\. What Information Do We Collect?**

There is no “account” feature on this website and therefore there is no sign-up opportunity where personal data such as name or email address will be requested.

**1a. We Use Cookies to Make Our Service Better and secure our systems**

A cookie is a small piece of information that is placed on your computer when you visit our website. We use these cookies to measure how many people use our website and the overall website performance, protect our systems from fraudulent or malicious traffic, and enable the display of advertising from our partners.

These partners may also collect, receive and use personal data and use cookies of their own to deliver personalised ads.

**Acceptance of Cookies**

By continuing your navigation of this website, you accept that cookies will be set and collected. If you are within the EEA, you are presented with an opportunity on your first visit to this website to accept or manage cookies. EEA users also always have the choice to manage these cookies at any time by using our cookie preferences dialog.  

A small number of cookies that we set are considered strictly necessary for the proper functioning of our website. These include:

\- A cookie that is set to remember your cookie consent decision

\- Cookies that are set to help protect against malicious or fraudulent website traffic

\- Cookies that are used for ad measurement and fraud protection

You cannot opt-out of these cookies using our cookie preferences dialog. If you do still wish to opt-out of these necessary cookies, you can do so by managing cookies at the browser-level. More information about how to do this is provided below.

**Managing Cookies at the Browser-level**

You may prefer to manage cookies at the browser-level. All modern browsers allow you to change your cookie settings. You can usually find these settings in the Options or Preferences menu of your browser. To understand these settings, the following links to external resources may be helpful, or you can use the Help option in your browser for more details.

[Cookie settings in Safari web](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH17191?locale=en_US) and [iOS](http://support.apple.com/kb/HT1677).

**1b. Our Analytics Software and Services Do Not Collect Your IP Address**

We use analytics software and services to measure how many people use this website and the overall performance of our website. We have configured the software and services to not collect your IP address or identify you personally in any way.

**1c. IP Addresses for Service Integrity and Security**

On the Internet, each device for transmitting data requires a unique address, the so-called IP address. The temporary storage of IP addresses is necessary for the proper functioning of the Internet. Public Holidays Global logs IP addresses on our servers to ensure our servers are operating correctly and not being compromised in any way by fraudulent or malicious traffic sources. Our logs typically only store an IP address for one week before the record is deleted.

**2\. How Can You Access and Update Your Personal Information?**

Public Holidays Global does not retain any personal identifiable information, except as specified in “IP Addresses for Service Integrity and Security” above.

**3\. Other Websites**

Our website may, from time to time, contain links to the websites of advertisers and other third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check their policies before you submit any personal data to those websites.

**4\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post the changes on this page. Please check the website regularly for any changes to this policy.

_This Privacy Policy was last updated on 27 September 2018._

**5\. Identity of Public Holidays Global**

If you are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy you may contact us using the information below.

Public Holidays Global  
Suite 180  
F78B/24-32 Lexington Drive  
Bella Vista NSW 2153 Australia  
E-mail: hello@publicholidays.global
